Guide to the Mark Hall Amitin/ World of Culture for the Performing Arts, Inc. Archive MSS.121
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series IV: World of Culture
  - Lo st Paradise screenplay, undated (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Charles Ludlam Memorial, July 13, 1987. (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Karen Ludwig - Broadway Bound, 1986 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Karen Ludwig - Help, Collision Course, Big Shot, Stanley and Iris, 1985-1988 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Mabou Mines contract with University of Pennsylvania, 1983 (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - Mabou Mines correspondence, bookings, 1982-1984 (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - Mabou Mines - Dead End Kids, 1982 (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - Mabou Mines - flyers, programs, 1981 (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - Mabou Mines - Japan, 1984 (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - Mabou Mines press, 1980- (Box 52, Folder 20)
  - Mabou Mines promotional material, 1983 (Box 52, Folder 21)
  - Mabou Mines - technical, 1982 (Box 52, Folder 22)
  - Mabou Mines - travel, 1984 (Box 52, Folder 23)
  - Mabou Mines - Warrior Ant travel, 1988 (Box 52, Folder 24)
  - Katie MacNichol, 1991 (Box 52, Folder 25)
  - Madonna video, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 26)
  - Ruth Malaczech, 1986 (Box 52, Folder 27)
  - Judith Malina - The Addams Family contracts, corespondence, 1990 (Box 52, Folder 28)
  - Judith Malina - The Addams Family press, publicity, 1991 (Box 52, Folder 29)
  - Judith Malina - The Addams Family press, 1991 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142040618095
  - Judith Malina - The Addams Family press, 1991 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Judith Malina - The Addams Family shooting schedule, Dec 1990 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Judith Malina - The Addams Family shooting schedule, 1990-1991 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Judith Malina - Woody Allen film, 1985 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Judith Malina - Mark Amitin letter to Wesleyan University, September 15, 1986 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Judith Malina - Angel Heart, 1996 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Judith Malina audition, undated (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Judith Malina - Awakenings, 1989-1990 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Judith Malina - Big City Blues, 1996 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Judith Malina - China Girl, 1986-1987 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Judith Malina - The Deli, 1996-1997 (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Judith Malina - Enemies, 1989 (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Judith Malina - E.R., 1996 (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Judith Malina - Frannie, 1992 (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Judith Malina - The Good Son, 1991 (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - Judith Malina - Household Saints, 1992 (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Judith Malina - Household Saints contracts, 1992 (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - Judith Malina - The Jerky Boys, 1994 (Box 53, Folder 19)
  - Judith Malina - Love is War, 1991 (Box 53, Folder 20)
  - Judith Malina - Men Lie, 1994 (Box 53, Folder 21)
  - Judith Malina - Miami Vice, 1987 (Box 53, Folder 22)
  - Judith Malina - Missing Reward, 1988 (Box 53, Folder 23)
  - Judith Malina - Music From Another Room, 1997 (Box 53, Folder 24)
  - Judith Malina - Paris Scramble, 1996 (Box 53, Folder 25)
  - Judith Malina residuals, 1983-1996 (Box 53, Folder 26)
  - Judith Malina - The Secret of My Success, 1986 (Box 53, Folder 27)
  - Judith Malina - The Sopranos, 1997 (Box 53, Folder 28)
  - Judith Malina - The Street, undated (Box 53, Folder 29)
  - Judith Malina - television, 1997 (Box 53, Folder 30)
  - Judith Malina - Tell me How's Paradise, 1996 (Box 53, Folder 31)
  - Judith Malina - Tribeca, 1992 (Box 53, Folder 32)
  - Judith Malina - Wait Until Spring, Bandini, 1989 (Box 53, Folder 33)
  - Karen Malpede, 1983-1988 (Box 53, Folder 34)
  - Freddie Mao, 1980- (Box 53, Folder 35)
  - Wayne Maugans, 1981-1994 (Box 53, Folder 36)
  - Wayne Maugans - As the World Turns, 1992 (Box 53, Folder 37)
  - Wayne Maugans - Lusting After Pipino's Wife, 1991 (Box 53, Folder 38)
  - James Mellon, 1977-1990 (Box 53, Folder 39)
  - James Mellon press, 1985-1992 (Box 53, Folder 40)
  - Greg Mehrten, undated (Box 54, Folder 1)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142040618103
  - Middlebury College, 1985-1992 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Angela Mohn, 1992 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Leslie Mohn, 1990-1992 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Mondo Beyondo contracts, correspondence, 1987 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Mondo Beyondo script, press, 1988 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Moon Over Parador, 1987 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Jean-Paul Moreau - Richard III, 1990 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Ica Mueller - A Cannibal in Manhattan, 1987-1988 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - David Mulkey, 1990 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Jeffrey Nash, undated (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Roy Nathanson, 1990-1994 (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Roy Nathanson / Jazz Passengers press, 1988-1992 (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - National Association for Drama Therapy, 1984 (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - National Education Theatre Conference, August 1986. (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - New School advanced acting, undated (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - New School auditioning class, 1991 (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - New School auditioning class, 1992 (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - New School class roster, undated (Box 54, Folder 19)
  - New School scene study class, undated (Box 54, Folder 20)
  - New School scene study class, 1991-1992 (Box 54, Folder 21)
  - New School teaching, 1990-1992 (Box 54, Folder 22)
  - New School workshops, undated (Box 54, Folder 23)
  - Mark Nizer, 1990-1992 (Box 54, Folder 24)
  - Mark Nizer - The Art of Juggling, undated (Box 54, Folder 25)
  - Mark Nizer calendar, 1990-1992 (Box 54, Folder 26)
  - Mark Nizer - Lincoln Center, 1992 (Box 54, Folder 27)
  - Mark Nizer - Lincoln Center Out of Doors, 1991 (Box 54, Folder 28)
  - Mark Nizer - Riverside Resort, December 17, 1990. (Box 54, Folder 29)
  - Nicky Paraiso, 1992 (Box 54, Folder 30)
  - Rob Parker, 1983-1989 (Box 54, Folder 31)
  - The Passion, 1987 (Box 54, Folder 32)
  - Thomas Pawluk, undated (Box 54, Folder 33)
  - The Performance Group, undated (Box 54, Folder 34)
  - Craig Peritz, undated (Box 54, Folder 35)
  - Philippe Petit brochures, 1973- (Box 54, Folder 36)
  - Philippe Petit, On the Hire Wire, 1985 (Box 54, Folder 37)
  - Philippe Petit press, 1971- (Box 54, Folder 38)
  - Philippe Petit resume, undated (Box 54, Folder 39)
  - Brad Phillips, undated (Box 54, Folder 40)
  - Playbills, programs, 1980s (Box 54, Folder 41)
  - Players Guide, 1988 (Box 54, Folder 42)
  - Playwriting awards, fellowships, 1995 (Box 54, Folder 43)
  - Postcards from America, 1990-1995 (Box 54, Folder 44)
  - David Quane, 1993 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142040618129
  - Rosemary Quinn, 1993 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Rosemary Quinn - The Balcony, 1988 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Quiz Show, 1989 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Ellen Ratner, 1985- (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Reading lists, undated (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Resumes (originals), undated (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Resumes and headshots, undated (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Resumes and headshots, undated (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Resumes and headshots, undated (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Resumes and headshots, undated (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Resumes and headshots, undated (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Resumes out to:, undated (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Hanon Reznikov, 1993 (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - Lawrence Sacharow, 1989 (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - Leeny Sack - The Survivor and the Translator, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - San Francisco Mime Troupe, 1983-1999 (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - David Schechter, 1978-1992 (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - David Schechter accounting, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - David Schechter - The Balcony, 1990 (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - David Schechter - Groundhog, 1990-1992 (Box 55, Folder 21)
  - David Schechter - Our Country's Good, 1990 (Box 55, Folder 22)
  - David Schechter - The Street, undated (Box 55, Folder 23)
  - David Schechter - Threepenny Opera, 1989 (Box 55, Folder 24)
  - Slava Schoot, undated (Box 55, Folder 25)
  - Screenwriting fellowship, 1990 (Box 55, Folder 26)
  - Screen Actors Guild, 1985-1988 (Box 55, Folder 27)
  - Serious Fun at Lincoln Center (Paul Zaloom) - correspondence, playbils, publicity, 1988-1989 (Box 55, Folder 28)
  - Richard Sheinmel - Scenes From the Plague Year, 1991-1993 (Box 55, Folder 29)
  - Stuart Sherman, 1990-1993 (Box 55, Folder 30)
  - Evanly Shin, 1986-1988 (Box 55, Folder 31)
  - Evanly Shin - Levis, 1987 (Box 55, Folder 32)
  - Mary Shultz - Anti-Defamatory League film, 1992 (Box 55, Folder 33)
  - Mary Shultz - Baltimore Waltz, 1993 (Box 55, Folder 34)
  - Mary Shultz - Mad Forest, 1991-1992 (Box 55, Folder 35)
  - Mary Shultz - Pacific Bell, 1993 (Box 55, Folder 36)
  - Mary Shultz - Quiz Show, 1993 (Box 55, Folder 37)
  - Michael Shurtleff - I Heard the Mermaids Singing, 1987 (Box 55, Folder 38)
  - James Siena, 1987 (Box 55, Folder 39)
  - Squat theatre, 1977-1986 (Box 55, Folder 40)
  - Squat Theatre, 1978-1983 (Box 55, Folder 41)
  - Squat Theatre - Andy Warhol's Last Love technical, undated (Box 55, Folder 42)
  - Squat Theatre - Dreamland Burns script, undated (Box 55, Folder 43)
  - Squat Theatre - Dreamland Burns technical, undated (Box 55, Folder 44)
  - Squat Theatre - Dreamland Burns U.S. press, 1985 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142040618111
  - Squat Theatre flyers, programs, 1977 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Squat Theatre - L Train to Eldorado, 1983 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Squat Theatre - Mr Dead and Mrs Free technical, undated (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Squat Theatre - New Observations 40, 1986 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Squat Theatre - Pig, Child, Fire! Technical, undated (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Squat Theatre - resume and press, 1970-1985 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Shirley Stoler, 1970- (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Shirley Stoler accounting, 1986 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Shirley Stoler - After School, 1986 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Shirley Stoler - Chief Zabu, 1986 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Shirley Stoler - The Deer Hunter, 1979 (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Shirley Stoler - Gersh contract, 1985 (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Shirley Stoler - Miami Blues, 1988 (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - Shirley Stoler - One Life to Live, 1986 (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - Shirley Stoler - Pee Wee's Playhouse, 1986 (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - Shirley Stoler - Rodney Dangerfield special, 1986 (Box 56, Folder 17)
  - Shirley Stoler - Sons, Topsy & Bunker, 1988 (Box 56, Folder 18)
  - Shirley Stoler - Sticky Fingers, 1987 (Box 56, Folder 19)
  - Shirley Stoler - Three O'Clock High, 1986 (Box 56, Folder 20)
  - Józef Szajna article, undated (Box 56, Folder 21)
  - Talent agencies, 1990 (Box 56, Folder 22)
  - Taper, Too, 1986 (Box 56, Folder 23)
  - Theater of Dreams, 1991 (Box 56, Folder 24)
  - Michael Tighe, 1987 (Box 56, Folder 25)
  - Chris Torch/ Jordcirkus, 1983- (Box 56, Folder 26)
  - Claude Underwood, 1992 (Box 56, Folder 27)
  - An Unfinished Song, 1990 (Box 56, Folder 28)
  - The Untouchables, 1986 (Box 56, Folder 29)
  - Andrew van Dusen - Legwork, Last Exit to Brooklyn, 1987 (Box 56, Folder 30)
  - Jean-Claude van Itallie, 1967-1999 (Box 56, Folder 31)
  - Jean-Claude van Itallie - The Balcony, 1988 (Box 56, Folder 32)
  - Jean-Claude van Itallie - correspondence, 1983- (Box 56, Folder 33)
  - Jean-Claude van Itallie - Japan, 1981 (Box 56, Folder 34)
  - Jean-Claude van Itallie - lectures, 1985 (Box 56, Folder 35)
  - Jean-Claude van Itallie - press, 1992 (Box 56, Folder 36)
  - Jean-Claude van Itallie - The Traveller, Dec 21, 1987 (Box 56, Folder 37)
  - Jean-Claude van Itallie - The Zen of Playwriting, undated (Box 56, Folder 38)
  - Jean-Claude van Itallie & Joseph Chaikin - Struck Dumb, Dec 21, 1987 (Box 56, Folder 39)
  - Jean-Claude van Itallie & Joseph Chaikin - Struck Dumb& letter from van Itallie, 1987 (Box 56, Folder 40)
  - Ron Vawter, 1987 (Box 56, Folder 41)
  - Ron Vawter - The Equalizer, The Street, 1987 (Box 56, Folder 42)
  - Ron Vawter - Sterling, 1988 (Box 56, Folder 43)
  - Video artists, undated (Box 56, Folder 44)
  - Videotapes of American theatre, undated (Box 56, Folder 45)
  - Paul von Canon, 1993 (Box 56, Folder 46)
  - Doug von Nessen, 1993 (Box 56, Folder 47)
  - Thomas Walker, 1992 (Box 56, Folder 48)
  - T. Weir Wright (handwritten note), undated (Box 56, Folder 49)
  - Gina Wendkos publicity brochure, undated (Box 56, Folder 50)
  - The Working Playground board meeting, Dec 28, 1992 (Box 56, Folder 51)
  - WOC accounting, 1982 (Box 56, Folder 52)
  - WOC American Express grants, 1984 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142040618137
  - WOC Amitin workshops, 1989 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - WOC board members (letters), 1997 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - WOC bookings for clients, 1987 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - WOC budget proposal, 1993 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - WOC business (general), 1985-1991 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - WOC casting labels, undated (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - WOC casting submissions, 1985 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - WOC casting submissions, Dec 1986-Aug 1987 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - WOC casting submissions, Dec 1987-Sep 1988 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - WOC client accounts, 1986 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - WOC client cards, undated (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - WOC client statements, Nov 1992-Dec 1992 (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - WOC client statements, 1993 (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - WOC computer, 1989-1990 (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - WOC correspondence, 1980-1985 (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - WOC correspondence, 1986-1990 (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - WOC correspondence, 1991- (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - WOC Enterprise Travel, 1984-1985 (Box 57, Folder 19)
  - WOC Enterprise Travel, 1985 (Box 57, Folder 20)
  - WOC film and video rentals, 1982-1990 (Box 57, Folder 21)
  - WOC form letter, undated (Box 57, Folder 22)
  - WOC mailing, undated (Box 57, Folder 23)
  - WOC media lists, undated (Box 57, Folder 24)
  - WOC messenger charges, undated (Box 57, Folder 25)
  - WOC National Conference of Personal Managers, 1985- (Box 57, Folder 26)
  - WOC National Conference of Personal Managers certificates, 1985 (Box 57, Folder 27)
  - WOC photocopy machine, 1986 (Box 57, Folder 28)
  - WOC Players' Directory, 1988 (Box 57, Folder 29)
  - WOC press clippings, 1983-1999 (Box 57, Folder 30)
  - WOC Rafik, 1986 (Box 57, Folder 31)
  - WOC sample artwork, undated (Box 57, Folder 32)
  - WOC Society of Stage Directors and Choreographers, 1989 (Box 57, Folder 33)
  - WOC stationery, undated (Box 57, Folder 34)
  - WOC tax forms, 1988 (Box 57, Folder 35)
  - WOC Tours, 1984 (Box 57, Folder 36)
  - WOC Tours - China and Japan, 1984 (Box 57, Folder 37)
  - WOC Tours - NACA proposal, 1983 (Box 57, Folder 38)
  - WOC The Travel People, 1990 (Box 57, Folder 39)
  - WOC The Travel People, 1991 (Box 57, Folder 40)
  - The Wooster Group, 1984-2001 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142040618145
  - Zhang Xin, undated (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Paul Zaloom accounts, 1988 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Paul Zaloom - Alley Pond Environmental Center, 1988 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Paul Zaloom - Bennington, VT, 1989 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Paul Zaloom - Binghampton High School, 1989 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Paul Zaloom biographies, contracts, proposals, 1988- (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Paul Zaloom - Brooklyn Academy of Music proposal, 1990 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Paul Zaloom - Central Park Summerstage, 1989 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Paul Zaloom contracts, 1986 (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Paul Zaloom contracts, 1986 (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Paul Zaloom contracts for April tour, 1988 (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Paul Zaloom - du Maurier World Stage, 1986 (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - Paul Zaloom engagements, 1986- (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - Paul Zaloom engagements, 1986- (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - Paul Zaloom - The Equalizer, undated (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - Paul Zaloom - flyers, programs, 1986- (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - Paul Zaloom - Humboldt State University, 1988 (Box 58, Folder 18)
  - Paul Zaloom - Jacob's Pillow, 1988 (Box 58, Folder 19)
  - Paul Zaloom - Lower Manhattan Cultural Council, 1988 (Box 58, Folder 20)
  - Paul Zaloom - Maine Arts Inc., 1988 (Box 58, Folder 21)
  - Paul Zaloom - Movement Theatre International, 1989 (Box 58, Folder 22)
  - Paul Zaloom - National Performance Network, 1986 (Box 58, Folder 23)
  - Paul Zaloom - Nazareth College, 1989 (Box 58, Folder 24)
  - Paul Zaloom - N.E.A. application, 1987 (Box 58, Folder 25)
  - Paul Zaloom - O'Neill Theatre Center, 1989 (Box 58, Folder 26)
  - Paul Zaloom - original press kit, undated (Box 58, Folder 27)
  - Paul Zaloom - Performance Art Festival, 1989 (Box 58, Folder 28)
  - Paul Zaloom press, 1984- (Box 58, Folder 29)
  - Paul Zaloom - Quality: An American Crisis, undated (Box 58, Folder 30)
  - Paul Zaloom - Spoleto Festival, 1989 (Box 58, Folder 31)
  - Paul Zaloom - Sounds Grand series, 1989 (Box 58, Folder 32)
  - Paul Zaloom - technical, 1988-1989 (Box 58, Folder 33)
  - Paul Zaloom- Theatre Communications Group conference, 1988 (Box 58, Folder 34)
  - Paul Zaloom - Theatre of the Hudson Highlands, 1987 (Box 58, Folder 35)
  - Paul Zaloom - Theater of Trash, 1986 (Box 58, Folder 36)
  - Paul Zaloom - Theatre Three Productions, 1989 (Box 58, Folder 37)
  - Paul Zaloom - University of Wisconsin, 1989 (Box 58, Folder 38)
  - Paul Zaloom - Vermont Comedy Festival, 1989 (Box 58, Folder 39)
  - Paul Zaloom - Way Off Broadway, 1987 (Box 58, Folder 40)
  - Paul Zaloom - WNYC, 1987 (Box 58, Folder 41)
  - Paul Zaloom - Woodstock, 1989 (Box 58, Folder 42)
  - Paul Zaloom workshops, undated (Box 58, Folder 43)
- Series V: Videorecordings
  - Subseries A: Video Recordings - Access Copies
    Conditions Governing Access
    Access copies for some materials are available by appointment for reading room viewing and listening only. Please contact fales.library@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596.
    - The Living Theatre, The Brig, Antigone, Frankenstein, Signals Pass Through the Flames, [1]-1964 [2]-1984 [3]-1969 [4]-1984; ID: 121.0159 (Case 121.0159)
      General note
      Format: VHS
      Duration: 00:28:50
      Original Format: VHS
    - The Living Theatre, Frankenstein, Berlin, 1965; ID: 121.0163 (Case 121.0163)
      Duration: 01:57:27
    - CBS Camera Three: Why Alice I and II w/ footage of Manhattan Project "Alice in Wonderland", 12/1/1970, ID: 121.0148 (Case 121.0148)
      Duration: 00:59:00
      Original Format: 3/4" Umatic
    - The Living Theatre, Parsons School of Design, 12/1971, ID: 121.0172 (Case 121.0172)
      Duration: 00:33:30
      Original Format: 1/2" Open Reel
    - CBS Camera Three: Magic of Peter Brook I, Jerzy Grotowski II, [1971]; ID: 121.0145 (Case 121.0145)
      Duration: 00:58:00
    - Bread and Puppet Theatre in Washington Square, 5/22/1972, ID: 121.0139 (Case 121.0139)
      Duration: 00:09:30
    - TOLA's Latin American Fair of Opinion, Theatre & Revolution panel, Hunter College, New York City, March 15, 1972; ID: 121.0196 (Case 121.0196)
      Duration: 00:34:20
      Scope and Content
      Organization: Theatre of Latin America
      Participants:
      Augusto Boal, Julian Beck, Judith Malina, Bernard Dort, Clarence Duncan.
    - TOLA's Latin American Fair of Opinion, Theatre & Revolution panel, Hunter College, New York City, March 15, 1972; ID: 121.0199 (Case 121.0199)
      Duration: 00:34:15
    - TOLA's Latin American Fair of Opinion, Theatre & Revolution panel, Hunter College, New York City, March 15, 1972; ID: 121.0202 (Case 121.0202)
      Duration: 00:32:45
    - Camera Three Nightwalk I - II, 1973; ID: 121.0209 (Box Shared Fales 129, Cd 121.0209)
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
      Format: DVD
    - The Living Theatre, Seven Meditations 1, 4/1973, ID: 121.0187 (Case 121.0187)
      Duration: [00:32:00]
    - The Living Theatre, Seven Meditations 2, 4/1973, ID: 121.0190 (Case 121.0190)
      Duration: 00:32:00
    - The Living Theatre, Six Public Acts, 5/8/1975, ID: 121.0193 (Case 121.0193)
      Duration: 00:22:00
    - Theatre Now: Judith Malina and Julian Beck final tape, 4/23/1975, ID: 121.0205 (Case 121.0205)
      Duration: 00:07:00
    - CBS Camera Three: Conversations about Theatre I and II, 1979; ID: 121.0142 (Case 121.0142)
      Duration: 01:00:00
    - The Living Theatre, Paradise Now film by Marty Topp, 2/1981, ID: 121.0169 (Case 121.0169)
      Duration: 00:45:35
      Original Format: Betamax
    - "Andy Warhol's Last Love" by Squat Theatre, NY 1983, ID: 121.0218 (Box Shared Fales 129, Cd 121.0218)
      Duration: 00:55:00
    - The Living Theatre, excerpts from Masse Mensch, The Yellow Methuselah, The Archeology of Sleep, [1]-Unknown [2]-Unknown [3]-1983; ID: 121.0166 (Case 121.0166)
      Duration: 00:14:20
    - The Living Theatre promo tape, 10/17/1983, ID: 121.0175 (Case 121.0175)
      Duration: 00:11:30
    - The Living Theatre, Antigone Rehearsal, 1/15/1984, ID: 121.0152 (Case 121.0152)
      Duration: 01:03:00
    - The Living Theatre, The Archeology of Sleep, 1/1984, ID: 121.0156 (Case 121.0156)
    - [Conversations with Channer]: Julian Beck and Judith Malina Cable Interview, 4/10/1985, ID: 121.0136 (Case 121.0136)
      Duration: 00:59:30
    - [1] - Living w/ The Living Theatre w/ Nam June Paik; [2]-Excerpts from The Living Theatre, Retrospectacle: Homage to Julian Beck; [3]-The Living Theatre, Retrospectacle Part 1, 1986,1987; ID: 121.0178 (Case 121.0178)
      Duration: 01:21:00
    - [1] - The Living Theatre, Retrospectacle Part 2; [2]- Heavy Petting Part 1, [1]-1986/1987 [2]-1989; ID: 121.0181 (Case 121.0181)
      Duration: 01:30:29
    - [1] - Heavy Petting Part 2; [2] - [Julian Beck Performance], [1]-1989 [2]-Unknown; ID: 121.0184 (Case 121.0184)
      Duration: 00:38:27
    - "An Obstetrical Dilemma" Shami Chaikin, undated; ID: 121.0212 (Box Shared Fales 129, Cd 121.0212)
      Duration: 00:25:00
    - The Mondo Beyondo Show, undated; ID: 121.0215 (Box Shared Fales 129, Cd 121.0215)
      Duration: 01:01:00
  - Subseries B: Video Recordings - Originals
    Organized alphabetically by subject. Access copies may not be available yet. Please check with the Fales Archivist.
    - Paramount Pictures, The Addams Family electronic press kit - video recording, VHS, T-45, 1991 (Box 59, Folder ID: 121.0001)
    - Alien Comic's Full Moon Show- videorecording VHS, TDK T-120, VHS, May 16, 1992 (Box 59, Folder ID: 121.0002)
    - Alien Comic at La Mama - videorecording, VHS, Panasonic NV-T120-SP, May 7, 1998 (Box 59, Folder ID: 121.0003)
    - Alien Comic's Luna Macaroona- videorecording VHS, undated (Box 59, Folder ID: 121.0004)
    - Mark Amitin, Kirk Bailey, Alexa- videorecording VHS, Samsung T-120-HQ, undated (Box 59, Folder ID: 121.0005)
    - Mark Amitin Department of Theatre Vincennes 1 - video recording Â½" Open Reel, Scotch 1150ft., May 23, 1975 (Box 59, Folder ID: 121.0006)
    - Mark Amitin Department of Theatre Vincennes 2 - video recording Â½" Open Reel, Scotch 1150ft., May 23, 1975 (Box 59, Folder ID: 121.0007)
    - Jo Andres: 8 BC performances, excerpts from As per Jaggy Rout, and two dances from Franklin Furnace - video recording VHS, TDK T-120, 1984-1986 (Box 59, Folder ID: 121.0008)
    - Jo Andres, Before Your Eyes and Lucid Possession, selections - video recording VHS, [T-30], 1987 (Box 59, Folder 121.0009A)
    - Untitled, undated (Box 59, Folder 121.0009B)
    - Jo Andres, Losing Sight Not Visions, selections - video recording, VHS, Maxell T-120-HF, undated (Box 59, Folder ID: 121.0010)
    - Michael Anzalone- video recording VHS, Fuji T-120, undated (Box 59, Folder ID: 121.0011)
    - George Bartenieff in Laser Man- videorecording VHS, T-15, undated (Box 59, Folder ID: 121.0012)
    - Julian Beck in All My Children- videorecording Beta max, Maxell L-750, undated (Box 59, Folder ID: 121.0013)
    - Julian Beck at BAM - video recording Â½" Open Reel, Sony V-32, undated (Box 60, Folder ID: 121.0014)
    - Julian Beck at BAM - video recording Â½" Open Reel, Sony V-32, undated (Box 60, Folder ID: 121.0015)
    - Julian Beck and Judith Malina cable interview - video recording Betamax, RCA L-750, 1985 (Box 60, Folder ID: 121.0016)
    - Julian Beck on Live at Five WNBC - video recording VHS, Apr 18, 1985 (Box 60, Folder ID: 121.0017)
    - Julian Beck in Miami Vice- videorecording VHS, JVC T-120, Sep 27, 1985 (Box 60, Folder ID: 121.0018)